Dhanashree Kore | Mobile: +919833203176 | Location: Pune 411021

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhanashree-kore-62009482/ | Email: vhavaledhanashree@gmail.com koredhanashree@gmail.com

Professional Summary:

A passionate People Person & a focused leader engaged in improving productivity, increasing efficiency, and enhancing quality. *My forte includes HR Operations with Business Partnering, HR Process & Policy formation, OD initiatives, Employee relation & Engagement, HRIS implementations, Offer negotiations, Employee attendance, and Payroll, SOC/ISO audits. Training & transforming internal talent into better professionals.*

HR professional with over 8.8 years of experience in HR Operation, OD & Change Management, & Business Partnering. Well versed in the strategic planning and execution of strategies for increasing net worth through networking. Collaborate well with human resources staff and hiring managers & leadership at all levels.

Functional competencies:-

HR Operations	HR Strategy & Policies	HR System Implementation	Leadership Development &
	Processes		Support
HK Business Partnering	Employee Engagement & Relations	SOC/ISO Audits	Performance Management
Employee Development & Training	Vendor Management		Change Management / Company Branding

Educational Qualification	Passing Year
POSH Certified Trainer (SkillDeck)	2023
Advanced Diploma in Business Administration (PGDBA HR) Welingkar - Mumbai	2013
Bachelor of Business Administration: Service Sector Marketing MITSOM College	2011

Accolade

- Was invited as a Guest Speaker for addressing the passing out Graduate students of Business Administration 2017 batch in MITCON Institute of Management
- Was invited as a Guest Speaker for addressing the MBA Induction 2017 batch in MITCON Institute of Management
- Freelancing as a Soft skills trainer (interview skills & part of soft skills) for a private class BE students.
- Visiting faculty for HRM & BO subjects in BVP New Law College since January 2018 till April 2018

Work History

Company: AMs Project Consultants Pvt. Ltd., Camp, Pune

Role: HR Manager | Duration: 08/2023 - Current

Talent Management & OD

- Propagate culture
- Manage induction for faster onboarding revised the methods and process of induction for better engagement.
- Nurture talent, enable L&D to meet business needs designed & implemented quarterly plans for training as per the business requirements and project needs.
- Create Performance driven culture designed R&R, implemented PMS.
- Branding, engaging with digital agency for developing posts etc.

Talent Operations

- Run efficient HR processes streamlined the onboarding & exit process, implemented PIP process, imbibed the usage of google workspace with the HRD.
- Enable Data driven decisions introduced & implemented monthly HR Dashboard for Sr. Management.
- Timely execution of HR processes
- Ensure organization is following statutory compliances as per the set standards revised & implemented the PF compliance as per the current rules.
- Little or no grievance because of HR processes implemented HR Helpdesk project to drive it through a data driven approach.
- Systems and Metrics to drive decisions implemented various google forms to systematically handle the employee data while onboarding & exits.
- Employee friendly Payroll and finance processes leading to higher Employee Self Service analyzing the loopholes for current HRMS (Keka) & filling in the gaps for the swift functioning of the system.

Talent Acquisition:

- Enable the business with right talent in terms of skills, attitude and potential revisiting the traditional approach towards hiring & implementing agile approach as per the needs.
- Facilitate in finding and onboard candidates into the organization networking with colleges, industry
 professionals to leverage the hiring.
- Reduce the cost of talent acquisition prioritizing the positions and implementing the cost effective measures to minimize the revenue loss of the organization.

Overall

- Create an integrated HR Strategy, roadmap, operating model
- Drive the employee feedbacks & surveys
- Timely communication for the effective communication of organizational & change management initiatives
- Focussed brand building working with Marketing
- Engage the Management layer with 1-1 connect, counseling, effective communication techniques, etc.

Company: Bitwise, Baner, Pune

Role: Sr. HR - Talent Engagement & Development | Duration: 02/2023 - 07/2023

- Handling the responsibilities pertaining to Employee Engagement programs
- Driving the team engagements along with the HRBP's for the project teams
- Ideating various methods of the employee engagement activities for the organization.
- End to end implementation of Microsoft Viva Engage project for org wide employee engagement purposes.
- Collaborate with the senior managers for planning & end to end coordination of the various internal + client visit events.
- Prepare & present the yearly engagement plans and budgeting for the org wide employee engagement & further push for approvals.
- Quarterly Microsoft teams engagement programme analytics and planning for further improving the virtual & physical engagement.

Company: AlphaSense, Balewadi, Pune

Role: People Operations Associate | Duration: 04/2021 - 02/2023

- Handling the responsibilities pertaining to Onboarding, Employee Engagement, Exit & People Operations
- Handle the quarterly ongoing training plans with end-to-end coordination
- Design and implement HR solutions as per the business need, and communicate effectively for the organizational change processes
- Advising & proposing changes for improved employee engagement and job satisfaction
- Projects handled & implemented E2E HR Helpdesk; Alpha-Connect google site
- Oversee daily office operations of the Pune/Mumbai office & HR department and while handling a team of two.
- Medical/Accident/Life policy execution & communication for benefits
- Conducting employee orientation and facilitating newcomers joining formalities
- Understand what the business expects and align organizational structure on strategic business objectives to help make an impact
- Research and analyze employee trends to understand ways to increase employee engagement and retention
- Plan & execute all employee engagement activities, communication within teams and the company for such
 activities, achievement communication, and related planning, etc. Handle the entire event from start to end
 without assistance and make it relevant and engaging for the employee single-handedly
- Checking & researching the gifting options available to give to the employees on various occasions (teamwise, organization-wide)
- Handle the planning, budgeting, and end-to-end managing and coordination of the various organization-wide events planned for the year. Preparing the events calendar and driving the India events team to meet the planned goals
- Provide required help in the onboarding process and be entirely responsible for Pre and Post joining responsibilities, managing the documentation, EDM, and background verification
- Travel & Visas Initiating the visa appointment, helping applicants with the documentation, preparing covering/invitation letters, and coordinating with the travel agency for the smooth processing of the visas

Company: BMC Consultancy Services Pvt. Ltd. (COVID Impacted)

Role: Sr. HR Lead, Bavdhan, Pune | Duration: 04/2019 - 03/2020

- Handling a team of HR & Admin (direct reporting 6 team members)
- Employee engagement planning and execution, Employee grievance handling

- Statutory compliance activities (PF/PT)
- Manpower planning and strategizing the recruitment plans for hiring
- Handling end-to-end employee life cycle (Hire to Retire)
- Offer Negotiations, Joining formalities
- Attendance & payroll management
- Planning, strategizing, and Implementation of internal HRIS as per organizational needs
- Exit formalities (F&F, Exit letters, etc.)
- Stationery, Housekeeping stock maintenance, Vendor management
- Medical policy strategizing and execution

Company: Vinsys IT Services India Pvt Ltd, Kothrud Pune

Role: Associate Sourcing Manager, Duration: 10/2018 - 03/2019

- Handling RMS(resource management solutions system) for sourcing freelance trainers on various technologies
- Managing vendors for sourcing trainers
- Handling end-to-end training coordination for various clients
- Handling Maharashtra region for SHTD (source-hire-train-deploy) model

Company: Webonise Lab, Bavdhan, Pune

Role: HR Consultant, Duration: 07/2018 - 08/2018

- Managing recruitment vendors for sourcing candidates on various technologies
- Managing & adding up new vendors for enhancing the smooth recruitment process for various positions
- Vendor negotiation, candidate negotiation, and joining initiation with the selected candidates

Company: Vikvins Consultants Pvt Ltd (Manpower Management division of Vinsys), Kothrud Pune

Role: Lead Recruiter, Duration: 02/2017 - 01/2018

- Handling the internal L&D for Vinsys IT Services (I) Pvt. Ltd.
- Identifying the training needs with the line managers/team managers
- Creating training outline & training plan for the sessions planned
- Creating & maintaining the training records (ISO records)
- Handling a team of 3 recruiters & 2 interns
- Working on the digital marketing front for Vikvins
- Training & Implementation of ATS within the team
- SPOC for the IT clients & handling the IT requirements; RPO clients
- Handling recruitment lifecycle for clients & fulfilling their L3 & L4 requirements (Non-IT)

Company: Vinsys IT Services India Pvt Ltd, Kothrud Pune

Role: Sr. Executive HR (Generalist), Duration: 07/2014 - 05/2016

- Handling the entire Employee Life Cycle (Onboarding, Induction, HR Policies, Asset allocation, Exit formalities)
- L&D activities for internal employees
- Employee Database Maintenance
- Employee Engagement & Employee Retention
- Recruitments & Client Management
- Internal Committees Management (CSR, Event, Sports)
- Employee Grievance handling
- Training & Development planning, execution, etc.
- Performance Management, Vendor Management
- HRIS (Implementation), ISO 9001-2008 process documentation
- Achievements: Awarded as "SHINING STAR HRD" for the year 2015-16

Company: Xed Intellect Pvt. Ltd., Pune

Role: Placement Officer, Duration: 08/2013 - 07/2014

- Handling recruitment, Joining formalities, and, Employee engagement activities
- HR Coordinator and single point of contact for the recruitment product XedScore
- Handling a team of HR and Marketing Interns for their SIP
- Responsible for co-coordinating with the clients, viz. HR recruiters, College and placement officers, students
- Responsible for innovations and strategy formations for the product XedScore and Xed News android application

Company: AMs Project Consultants Pvt. Ltd., Pune

Role: HR & Admin Executive, Duration: 04/2012 - 09/2012

- Implement & monitor various HR initiatives and activities.
- Responsibility includes employment, compensation, training, and development.
- Interview job applicants, review applications/ resumes, evaluate applicants' skills and make recommendations regarding applicant's qualifications.
- Prepare and maintain job documentation, and job evaluation system in coordination with the respective department and

the authority.

- Complete appraisal system & payroll management
- Recommend, develop, and schedule training programs and development courses.
- HR policies & SOP drafting
- Employee grievances addressing
- Ensuring joining and exit formalities
- Taking care of Housekeeping (Cleanness), Infrastructure Management, Lodging and traveling arrangement
- Employee-related activities Access cards, Visiting cards, etc. Pantry operation (tea/coffee etc.) & catering service, Courier management

Company: IFCM HAM Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai

Role: Officer Recruiter | Duration: 12/2011 - 03/2012

- Independently handled clients like RohaDyechem and AryaOmnitalk
- Achieved 4 closures in 3 months' time span & 3 closures in IT and 1 closure for Head PPC
- Analyzing the requirements thoroughly on the basis of the required skill sets given by the clients & finding suitable resumes through internal references (database files) and external entities like search portals, Screening, Short-listing Candidates,
- Interview scheduling of the shortlisted candidates with the respective Functional Head
- Regular follow up with candidate from the first contact till the issue of offer letter to the joining of the candidate
- Managing database of profiles received through Advertisement responses against various position, categorizing in Vertical and Function wise, maintaining interviewed, Pending, Potential and Selected candidates records
- Maintaining & developing the complete database of the recruitment process inclusive of selected / on hold and rejected candidates
- Preparing weekly, monthly & quarterly MIS reports using Excel